# Mateusz Stankiewicz

#### Junior Front-end Developer

A highly motivated and reliable junior front-end developer with a passion for creating websites. Enjoy working as part of a team. Self-started, paying strong attention to detail. Eager to learn and develop knowledge and skills. Currently looking for a new and challenging position within a company where I could grow both personally and professionally. Come back home to Poland after six years spent abroad. Can work remotely.



- mateuszstankiewicz999@gmail.com
- Białystok, Poland
- matthewstanki.github.io
- github.com/matthewstanki

- +48 728034680 (Poland) | +44 7548163066 (England)
- 27 July, 1993
- linkedin.com/in/mateusz-stankiewicz
- instagram.com/matthewstanki

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### High reach FLT driver **DMW Logistics**

2016 - 2021

Sutton-in-Ashfield, England

• Loading and unloading materials from a variety of vehicles. Moving pallet-packed materials around the site or storage facility. Performing equipment checks and basic maintenance. Quality checking and counting stocks. Driving high reach FLT.

### Warehouse operative / Production worker (temporary work)

Freshstart Recruitment LTD / Senior Salmon Recruitment Agency

2015 - 2016

Nottinghamshire, England

• Work in various fast-paced environments such as Bonds Confectionery, Jigsaw Foods, Synseal Extrusions. Duties include picking and packing orders, loading and unloading goods from lorries, operating production line equipment, cleaning work areas.

## Bartender / Mixologist

**Pub Brama** 

2013 - 2015

Białystok, Poland

• Work in fast-paced and vibrant environment. Prepare and serve a range of alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks and cocktails. Keep the bar area clean and well stocked. Collect payment and operate tills.

### Material handler (part time)

Zinc Plating services

2013 - 2015

Białystok, Poland

• Prepare materials surfaces using water or hazardous chemicals. Assist and maintain the zinc plating line production. Apply safe work practices and procedures at all time.

German

### **EDUCATION**

# **University of Technology Białystok**

Front-end Development

2014 - 2015

Białystok, Poland

Web applications / Frontend Development

### **Secondary School No.7**

Language class

2010 - 2013 English

Białystok, Poland

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**



#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Portfolio(2020 - Present)

https://matthewstanki.github.io

My Parallax Movie Project (2020 - 2021)

https://my-parallax-movie-project.web.app

My Arsenal Blog (2019 - 2020)

https://arsenal-kanonierzy.web.app

LÓMË Premium Quality Sportswear (2018 - 2020)

• http://lome.azurewebsites.net

MatthewStanki99 School Project (2014 - 2015)

https://matthewstanki99.firebaseapp.com

### LANGUAGES

#### Polish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### English

• Full Professional Proficiency

#### German

Elementary Proficiency

### INTERESTS

Formula 1 Creating websites Football Gym MMA WW2 Movies Techno Video games